komu.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy

Here at KOMU.com, ("KOMU 8", "we" and "us"), we understand and respect your concerns about the use of your personal information. KOMU 8 supports a general policy of openness about personal data collection and use. We have adopted and implemented a privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") as part of our commitment to protecting your personal information from misuse. We believe that you should know what information about you we collect, as well as how that information is used, maintained, and, in some cases, shared. Any personal information provided by you to us through our website will be handled in accordance with our Privacy Policy, as set forth below.

We will collect information about you when you transmit information to us through our website or via email, when you sign up for our electronic newsletters, when you register for our promotions, when you upload material to our website, when you register for other online features and services we provide and when you otherwise use our website. By doing any of the foregoing, you assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not engage in any of these activities.

## Information Collected About You and Our Use of Such Information

The following describes the types of personal and other information we may collect about you, and how we use and maintain that information:

**Contact Information**

We collect your name, email address and other contact information you provide when you register for or subscribe to our email and text message newsletters, when you transmit information to us by email or via our website through features like the Contact Us page, the community calendar and the Hometown Highlights section, when you upload photos, videos, audio and/or written content to our website, when you register for or use other services and features we provide and when you otherwise use our website.

We will use information you provide only for the purpose for which you provide it. For example, we will use your information to respond to any inquiries you may submit to us. If you sign up for our electronic newsletters, we will use your information to manage your subscription to that newsletter and contact you with regard to that subscription. If you submit an item for our Hometown Highlights section, we may contact you to clarify information.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your use of our website, such as service announcements, administrative messages and communications regarding your subscription, or materials you have posted, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

**Online Information**

Our website collects aggregate information site-wide, including anonymous site statistics. In addition, when you visit our website our system automatically collects domain names, your IP address and the type of browser that you use. When you browse our website, our systems log the KOMU 8 web pages that you visit. This information may be used to analyze trends, administer the website, improve the design of our website, track user movement, and otherwise enhance the services we provide.

**Information from Promotions**

We will collect information you give us if you participate in a KOMU 8 promotion, such as a contest. You may be asked to provide your name and email address, and possibly other information such as your mailing address and telephone number.

We will store this information in our database and will use it to communicate with you about the promotion. We may also use this information to send you periodic publications or news associated with KOMU 8 in the future or promotional materials about KOMU 8, unless you inform us that you opt out from receiving such communications. If a promotion is done jointly with another entity, the information we collect may be shared with such third parties who have their own, separate privacy policies. In such a case, you should visit their website(s) to read each applicable privacy policy.

**Other Information**

We may retain any data you provide to us in an email or other inquiry, for the purpose of tracking the types of questions that we receive.

## When Your Information Will be Shared or Disclosed

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on KOMU 8, (b) protect and defend the rights of property of KOMU 8 or the users of our website, and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of our website or the public. We may use such information to establish or exercise our legal rights, or to defend against legal claims.

We reserve the right to disclose information about you, including data on which pages you have visited, to third parties if we feel it is necessary to protect our systems, business, users or others.

We may provide aggregate information, such as the number of users who have visited our website, to other parties. Only aggregate information is shared, no user specific information.

Information about you in our possession may also be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, sale of assets, or transition of service to another provider, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which your personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of KOMU 8. KOMU 8 does not guarantee that any entity receiving such information in connection with one of these transactions will comply with all terms of this Privacy Policy.

In addition, when you post content to certain features on our website, such as our community calendar or Hometown Highlights section, certain information you provide may be viewable by other users of our website. 

Notwithstanding anything contained herein, we may disclose personally identifiable information to other companies that we contract with to create, support, manage, maintain or improve our website and the features on our website.

**Security**

Whenever KOMU 8 handles information that you enter on our website, regardless of where this occurs, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, KOMU 8 cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

## Third Party Information

You agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose personal information you supply to us with regard to: (a) the purposes for which such third party's personal information has been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party's personal information; (c) which of the third party's information is obligatory and which information, if any, is voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the information held about them.

## Children's Privacy

If you are under the age of 13, please do not use or access our website in any way. We will not knowingly collect or use any personal information from such children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have collected any personal information from children under 13, we will promptly delete such information from our databases.

## Other Websites

For your convenience, our website may contain links to other websites, or you may be otherwise referred to other websites, including websites administered by the University of Missouri or administered by other companies on behalf of KOMU 8 or the University of Missouri, as well as to websites unrelated to KOMU 8 or the University of Missouri. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these linked websites. Each website should be checked for its own privacy policy.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

KOMU 8 may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. In the event that KOMU 8 merges with, or is acquired by another entity, a change to this Privacy Policy may result. Whenever a change to this Privacy Policy is significant, we will place a prominent notice on our website.

## Governing Law

By choosing to visit our website or otherwise provide information to KOMU 8, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the laws of the State of Missouri. You also agree to arbitrate such disputes and to abide by any limitation on damages contained in our Terms of Service (available at <https://www.komu.com/pages/terms-of-service>) or other agreement we have with you

## Updating You Information or Giving Suggestions

If you would like to update or correct any information that you have provided to KOMU 8 through your use of this website or otherwise, or you have suggestions for improving this Privacy Policy, please send an email to [webmaster@komu.com](mailto:webmaster@komu.com).

Effective Date: November 7, 2007
